Harrison S. Morris Papers, 1784-1970 (bulk 1895-1935 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
Harrison S. Morris Papers
1895-1935
1784-1970
C0003
Princeton University Library. Special Collections. Manuscripts Division One Washington Road Princeton, New Jersey 08544 USA
139.4 linear feet 341 boxes
Morris, Harrison S. (Harrison Smith), 1856-1948
Consists of the personal papers of Philadelphia author, businessman, and philanthropist Harrison S. Morris.
Harrison Smith Morris was born in Philadelphia on October 4, 1856, the son of George Washington and Catharine (Harris) Morris. He had two younger sisters, Matilda Harris Morris and Jane Walters Morris, who never married. At the age of sixteen he went to work for the Reading Coal & Iron Company to help support his parents, who were in ill health. In 1893 he became the managing director of the Philadelphia Academy of the Fine Arts, a position which he held until 1905. Morris also served as editor of Lippincott's Magazine, art editor of the Ladies' Home Journal, and chairman of the Ways and Means Committee of the National Academy of Design. From 1909-1917 he was president of the Wharton Steel Company. His activities brought him in contact with leaders in the artistic and literary world. He also wrote and published his own works, in both English and Italian, on Roman history, literature, and culture, as well as at least seventeen volumes of poetry, fiction, and essays.
Morris married Anna, daughter of Joseph Wharton, on June 2, 1896. Their only child, Catherine Wharton Morris, nicknamed "Kit," was born on January 26, 1899. Harrison Smith Morris died on April 12, 1948. Anna Wharton Morris died on June 21, 1957, at the age of eighty-eight. Catharine "Kit" Morris Wright died in 1988.
The collection consists of the personal papers of Morris, which reflect his interest in the world of letters, art, business, and government, as well as the social world of Philadelphia. The collection includes his original manuscripts for novels ( Hannah Bye and The Landlord's Daughter), poetry ( A Duet in Lyrics, Lyrics and Landscapes, and Madonna and Other Poems), short stories ( Tales from Shakespeare and Tales from Ten Poets), essays ( Papers to Put in Your Pipe), non-fiction ( Confessions in Art), biographies ( Walt Whitman and William T. Richards), and book reviews which appeared in periodicals such as Scribner's Magazine, Ladies' Home Journal, and the Century Magazine. Also included are the original manuscripts for "Books of the Month" published in Lippincott's Magazine.
Much of the collection is related to the American art world of the late nineteenth and early twentieth centuries, including correspondence from such artists as John La Farge, Joseph Pennell, J. Alden Weir, William M. Chase, Cecilia Beaux, Childe Hassam, Violet Oakley, J. McClure Hamilton, Elihu Vedder, and the sculptor Augustus S. Gaudens, to name but a few. Also, there are papers from institutions of art such as the Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, the Corcoran Gallery, the Art Association of Newport (R.I.), the Albright Art Gallery, the Buffalo Fine Arts Museum, the Boston Museum of Fine Arts, the St. Louis Art Museum, and the National Academy of Design. In addition, the records of the Rome International Art Exposition of 1911, of which Morris was commissioner-general, are included. Additional papers contain family correspondence dating back to the 1860s, as well as a number of daguerreotypes of family members.
Morris’s papers reflect his interest in government at all levels, local, state, and national. Also included are the papers of Philadelphia societies and clubs such as the American Philosophical Society, the Browning Society, the Franklin Inn Club, and the Triplets. Morris was related by marriage to the Wharton and Lippincott families of Philadelphia, and his papers contain correspondence with many of the first families of the city. The Keats-Shelley Memorial Committee and the Hall of Fame are also represented. And there is lengthy correspondence between Morris and Robert Underwood Johnson who shared many literary interests, as well as material relating to Walt Whitman whose life and works were for Morris a life-long passion.
Organized into ten series.
The collection is open for research.
Gift of Catherine Wharton Morris Wright (daughter) on February 4, 1974.
No appraisal information is available.
Some of the manuscripts in this collection have been published. The following were published by J. B. Lippincott of Philadelphia: In the Yule-Log Glow (1892), Madonna and Other Poems (1894), Martial Notes (1929), Masterpieces of the Sea (1912), A Mosaic, Tales from Shakespeare (1893), and Tales from Ten Poets (1893). Also published were: Confessions in Art (N.Y.: Sears, 1930), A Duet in Lyrics (published privately by Harrison S. Morris with co-author John Arthur Henry, 1883), Hannah Bye (Phila.: Penn Publishing Co., 1920), The Landlord's Daughter (Phila.: Penn Publishing Co., 1923), Lyrics and Landscapes (N.Y.: The Century Co., 1908), Odes (published privately by Harrison S. Morris, 1938), and Walt Whitman (Cambridge: Harvard University Press, 1929).
The papers of Morris's wife, Anna Wharton Morris, are available at the Friends Historical Library at Swarthmore College.
Whitman, Walt, 1819-1892--Appreciation; Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Buffalo, N.Y.); Corcoran Gallery of Art; Museum of Fine Arts, Boston; National Academy of Design (U.S.); New York University. Hall of Fame; Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts; St. Louis Art Museum; Architects--United States--20th century--Correspondence; Art critics--United States--20th century--Correspondence; Art dealers--United States--20th century--Correspondence; Art schools--United States--20th century; Art societies--United States--20th century; Art, American--19th century; Art, American--20th century; Art--Exhibitions--20th century; Arts--United States--Management--20th century; Philadelphia (Pa.)--Intellecutal life--20th century; Correspondence; Daguerreotypes (photographs); Manuscripts; American literature; Art history; Art history; Photography; American literature
- Series 1: Writings, 1874-1944; 39.0 boxes
  This series consists of files of autograph and typed manuscripts of Morris's writings, often including correspondence, proofs, galleys, and related printed matter.
  Organized into subseries by form or genre, and within those subseries alphabetically by title.
  - Subseries 1A: Novels, 1919-1920; more than 3 boxes
    Consists of three novels written by Harrison Morris, 1919-1920.
    Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Hannah Bye, 1919-1920; 2.0 boxes
      Includes manuscripts, proofs, correspondence, publishing agreement, and printed matter.
    - The Landlord's Daughter, dates not examined; 1.0 box
      Includes Morris's agreement to publish with the Penn Publishing Co., 1921.
    - Romance of a Two-Story House, dates not examined; 2.0 boxes
  - Subseries 1B: Poetry, 1874 October 9-1942 August 4; 17.0 boxes
    Consists of manuscripts for poetry of Harrison Morris, including "Madonna and Other Poems", 1874-1942.
    - A Duet in Lyrics, dates not examined; 8.0 folders
      - "After a Shower at Sunset", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - "Lucrece", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - "Reconciliation", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - "Early April", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "Radiant Day", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - "Mine Oaten Pipe", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - Background information from Catherine Morris Wright, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - Printed Matter, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 5.0 folders
      - Where Meadows Meet the Sea Anthology, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - Copies of poems by Keats, Shelley, Milson, Swinburne, Whitman, etc., dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - Christmas Poems, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - Poetry Books--Youthful years, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - Works for "The Club" meeting announcements, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
    - In the Yule Log Glow, dates not examined; 2.0 boxes
      - Introductory Material, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - "Christmas in the Desert", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - "Christmas with a Cure", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - "Christmas with the Baron", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "How Steenwykerwold Was Saved", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - "The Italian Guest's Selection", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - "Mr. Grapewine's Christmas Dinner", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - "Salvette and Brenadou", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - "The Three Christmas Masses", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - "The Three Kings of Cologne", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - "Two Christmases", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - "The Wolf Tower", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - Book III (Poetry), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      - galley proofs--1, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - galley proofs--2, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous Material, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
    - Lyrics and Landscapes, 1885 December 20; 38.0 folders
      - "Ad Matrem", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - "After and Idle Night or Two", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - "An Inland Eclogue", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - "An Opossum", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "At Sunset", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - "A Wood Tryst", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - "The Ballad of the Chimes", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - "Compline", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - "Covetise", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - "Destiny", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - "Duality", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - "Exile", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - "Forest Fires in June", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      - "Incarnation", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
      - "Joseph Wharton--81 Years Old", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      - "May", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
      - "Midsummer Noon", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
      - "Night", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
      - "Poet and Potentate", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 19)
      - "Rebuke", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 20)
      - "Renaissance", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 21)
      - "Revelation", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 22)
      - "Singing Woods", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 23)
      - "Stars", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 24)
      - "Sunrise in Song", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 25)
      - "To a Flag-Flaver in a Almanac", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 26)
      - "The Gilded Gate", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 27)
      - "The Immigrants", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 28)
      - "The Rain-Drop Sonata" (Prelude)", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 29)
      - "The Three Kings", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 30)
      - "The Winds Dalliance", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 31)
      - "Vespers", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 32)
      - "Walt Whitman", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 33)
      - "Winter Twilight", 1885 December 20; 1.0 item (Folder 34)
      - Correspondence A-M, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 35)
      - Correspondence N-Z, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 36)
      - The Century Co., dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 37)
      - Press Review "The Bellman", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 38)
    - Madonna and Other Poems, dates not examined; 2.0 boxes
      - Title Page and Frontispiece, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - "Madonna", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - "The Lonely Bird", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - "Maryas", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "A Garden Quest", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - "Wood Robin", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - "The Daffodil", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - "Oracle", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - "To A Comrade", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - "Hay Scents", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - "To a Fallen Pine-Tree", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - "Parable", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - "Day Dreamerie", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      - "A Winged Oracle", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
      - "The Return of Spring", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      - "A Woodland Interview", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
      - "Landscape", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
      - "Three Weeks Before Spring", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
      - "Vespers", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 19)
      - "Mid-Days of June", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 20)
      - "Of a Little Brook", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 21)
      - "Sun in the Willow", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 22)
      - "Evening in the Fields", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 23)
      - "After a Week of Rain", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 24)
      - "The Cricket", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 25)
      - "Clouds at Sundown", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 26)
      - "The Passing Gust", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 27)
      - "August", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 28)
      - "To a Sycamore", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 29)
      - "The Day After Summer", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 30)
      - "Winds and Leaves", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 31)
      - "Through Fallen Leaves", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 32)
      - "One Weeping by the Wayside": proof, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 33)
      - "A Touch of Frost", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 34)
      - "Birds of Passage", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 35)
      - "October", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 36)
      - "November Snow-fall", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 37)
      - "Winter Sunset", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 38)
      - "Winter", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 39)
      - "Song", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 40)
      - "Naked Bough", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 41)
      - "You and I", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 42)
      - "Woodfellows", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 43)
      - "Fairy Gold", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 44)
      - "Succory", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 45)
      - "Clearing Off", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 46)
      - "To a Chrysanthemum", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 47)
      - "The Winter Wind", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 48)
      - "Sadie", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 49)
      - "The Earthworm", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 50)
      - "Storm", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 51)
      - "Douzabelle", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 52)
      - "A Pine Tree Buoy", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 53)
      - "Fickle Hope", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 54)
      - "A Primer", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 55)
      - "The Hermit Thrush", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 56)
      - "The Hedge", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 57)
      - "Mother of the Years", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 58)
      - "What Difference?", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 59)
      - "Reading Sartor Resartus", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 60)
      - "The Alsman", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 61)
      - "Leafless", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 62)
      - "The Dawn of Christmas", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 63)
      - "Good Night", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 64)
      - "Story", heading, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 65)
      - "Love's Revenge", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 66)
      - "Amymome", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 67)
      - "The Gravedigger", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 68)
      - "A Roadside Portrait", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 69)
      - "XVIII Sonnets", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 70)
      - "Frangrance and Song", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 71)
      - "To Poverty", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 72)
      - "Duality", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 73)
      - "Orchard-Lore", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 74)
      - "Homer", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 75)
      - "A Greek Panel", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 76)
      - "Atlanta", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 77)
      - "Mohammed and Seid", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 78)
      - "On Hearing and Old Piano", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 79)
      - "Sudden Noise in the Street", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 80)
      - "At Daylight", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 81)
      - "Oblivion", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 82)
      - "Wood-tryst", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 83)
      - "Incantation", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 84)
      - "A Touch of Nature", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 85)
      - "F. W.", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 86)
      - "Walt Whitman", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 87)
      - "At Walden Pond", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 88)
      - "Trivia", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 89)
      - "To Arcady", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 90)
      - "Under-Bough", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 91)
      - "Daphnis", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 92)
      - "A Rival of Orpheus", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 93)
      - "Witch-Music", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 94)
      - "An Idler's Catch", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 95)
      - "A Forest Catch", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - "Phyllis", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - "The Trystall Tree", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - "Lydian Airs", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "A Catch", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - "Catches", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - "A Wooing Catch", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - "A Change of Face", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - "Comrade Ease", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - "Arcady", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - "Of a Little Girl" ("Lady"), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - "Under-Tree", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - "A Modern Eclogue", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      - "The Footpath Way", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
      - "A Portrait of Distemper", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      - "After Rain", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous Material, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
      - Page Proofs, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 19)
      - Unbound Book, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 20)
    - Martial Notes of the Old War and the New, 1928 January 12; 2.0 boxes
      - "The Vanishing [Legion]", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - "Two Captains", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - "Unknown", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - "The Deserter", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "The Toothpick", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - "The Dedication", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - "At the Campfire" ("At a Campfire"), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - "At the Gettysburg Reunion", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - "Decoration Day At the Buryin' Ground", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - "The National Cemetery", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - "The Call of the Fire-Zouavcs", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - "Fifty Years After", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - "The Governor's Story" ("The Lad and Lincoln"), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      - "The Last Gray Reserve" ("The Sixtieth Gray Reserve"), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
      - "Hymn for Decoration Day", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      - "Bull Run Reserved", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
      - "Flag-Draped Coffins", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
      - "Separate Peace", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
      - "Italy Redeemed", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 19)
      - "Washington-April 1918", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 20)
      - "To Robert Underwood Johnson at Seventy-Five", 1928 January 12; 1.0 item (Folder 21)
      - "A Financier", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 22)
      - "To the Lady of Hamilton House" ("Hamilton House"), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 23)
      - "Rome", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 24)
      - "Rain IN June", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 25)
      - "An Interrupted Rhapsody", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 26)
      - "September Twilight", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 27)
      - "Creed", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 28)
      - "The Time's Clock", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 29)
      - "Wing and Wing", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 30)
      - "Beauty", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 31)
      - "Twilight", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 32)
      - "Batsto Dam", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 33)
      - "Pilgrim Fathers", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 34)
      - "Autumn", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 35)
      - "Autumn-Realized in Music", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 36)
      - "Shelley", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 37)
      - "William M. Chase", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 38)
      - "Madison Cawein", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 39)
      - "A la Pension" ("To a Female Boarder"), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 40)
      - "Journey's End", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 41)
      - Autographed carbons for: "The Toothpick," "Two Captains," "The Vanishing Legion," "At A Campfire," "Decoration Day," "Fifty Years After," "The Deserter", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - Title pages, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - Galley Proofs, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - Correspondence--G.A.R. Responses, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - Correspondence--re: "Flag-Draped Coffins", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - Correspondence--"Thank-you Notes", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - "For the Honor of the G.A.R." Publicity Release, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - Contract, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - Invoices: J. B. Lippincott, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
    - A Mosaic, 1891-1940; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)